Skúli Arnarsson

Looking for a full time job in web, software or app development

General information

SSN: 280995-2079

Address: Þrastahraun 1, 220, Hafnarfjörður

Email: skuliarnarsson@gmail.com

Mobile: 858-7111

Personal page: skulipardus.online GitHub: github.com/skulia15

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/skulipardus



About me

I am a 23 year old student at the University of Reykjavík studying computer science with a focus on web development and user interface design. My interests include everything related to technology, programming, alternative and electronic music, video games, exploring the world and experiencing different cultures. I'm a responsible and an extremely reliable employee. I am quick at learning and mastering new technologies and I like working alongside others in a team. I am most interested in working in web- or app development. I am healthy and don't smoke. I don't have a criminal record. I have a driver's licence and I own a car. I am fully willing to relocate anywhere.

Education

Reykjavík University – BSc Computer Science

August 2015 - December 2018, CURRENT GPA 8.74

BSc in computer science with a focus on web development and user interface design. I have finished 168 of 190 ECTS, so I have 2 courses remaining. I will sit the course Enterprise Systems as a distance student in the fall semester of 2018. I will also sit the three week course Quality Assurance and Testing in December in order to complete my focus in web development and user interface design.

Universidad Carlos III de Madrid (Exchange student)— BSc Computer Science

January 2017 - June 2017

Menntaskólinn við Hamrahlíð – Diploma(Stúdentspróf) from gymnasia

August 2011 - May 2015 GPA 8.90

Work experience

Programming languages

- Javascript
- C#
- Python
- C++
- Java C
- SOL
- (HTML5)
- (CSS)

Tools and technologies

- Vue.is
- React.is
- Xamarin
- Node.is
- **Express**
- ASP.NET
- RESTful web services
- .NET Framework
- Webpack
- Mocha
- Bookshelf.js











github.com/skulia15

// Jökulá, Advertising Agency- Internship

January 2018 -

My final Project for University of Iceland. We build a "Full Stack" web service / application from scratch. The web service is meant for in-house use at Jökulá . The web service handles allocation, supervision and record keeping for all of Jökulá's projects. The service is implemented using *Node.js* for back end functionality and the front end is implemented using *Vue.js*.

Straumhvörf — Night guard / Standard employee

June 2017 - January 2018

I worked part-time both as a night guard and as a standard employee. The job involved care for people who suffer from serious mental disorders.

Te & K affi — Barista

September 2014 - December 2017

I worked part-time as a barista. The job involved working the register, making coffee- and tea based drinks, washing dishes, cleaning and I prepared and waited food. I did everything needed to keep a coffeehouse up and running.

NFMH, Students association of Menntaskólans við Hamrahlíð – *Member of marketing committee*

January 2014 - May 2015

I was responsible for the acquisition of sponsorships and advertisements in collaboration with various companies to finance the students association.

ISS Iceland— Delivery driver

May 2014 - September 2014

I worked as a delivery driver for a summer. I drove around the capital area and delivered clean laundry to various companies and organizations. I also oversaw orders and maintenance in the warehouse I also did various other work in the laundry room.

ISS Iceland - Cleaner / Custodian

December 2009 - May 2014

I mostly worked with cleaning in a mall. I worked full-time in the summer and over Christmas, but otherwise I worked two days a week.

ISS - Cleaner

May 2013 - August 2013

I worked a summer job in public household services for older people and people with reduced mobility in Gardabær. I managed company vehicle.

- Pug
- Less
- Gulp
- Bootstrap
- Gi
- Agile Methodologies
- Istanbul
- Bash

Languages

Icelandic- Native language

English-Fluent

Spanish, Danish- Working knowledge

French, Italian- Little working knowledge

Grants

Freshmen grant from Reykjavík University - For excellent performance in gymnasia.

Erasmus+ grant - For participating in an Erasmus exchange program in Madrid.









Fínt slf — Cleaner

December 2009 - May 2014

General cleaning, cleaning and waxing floors. I worked part-time with school.

Morgunblaðið — Newspaper carrier

February 2007 - September 2007

I delivered newspapers every day of the week.

References

Gísli Rúnar Sævarsson - Owner at Fínt shf.

Phone: 6649099.

Email: gislirun@gmail.com.

Rakel Róbertsdóttir- Director at Straumhvörf.

Phone: 695-8501.

Jónína Gunnarsdóttir - Service representative at ISS.

Phone: 6964924.

Email: jonina@iss.is.









Academic record at Reykjavík University

The second second												
COURSE	COURSE NA	ME			GRADE	STATUS	RANKING	ECTS	SEMESTER	DATE		
T-107-TOLH	Computer Arc	<u>hitecture</u>			9,5	Completed	30-55/228	6	20153	06.11	.2015	Statistics
T-111-PROG	Programming				9	Completed	28-48/191	6	20153	06.11	.2015	Statistics
T-113-VLN1	Semester Pro	ject 1			8,5	Completed	185-222/263	6	20153	31.12	.2015	Statistics
T-114-VERK	Problem Solvi	ng .			9	Completed	60-123/251	6	20153	16.11	.2015	Statistics
T-117-STR1	Discrete Math	ematics I			8	Completed	23-36/173	6	20153	19.11	.2015	Statistics
T-201-GSKI	Data Structure	es es			8	Completed	63-86/204	6	20161	18.04	.2016	Statistics
T-213-VEFF	Web-Program	ming			9	Completed	33-64/242	6	20161	22.04	.2016	Statistics
T-216-GHOH	Software Req	uirements	and Design		9	Completed	13-34/224	6	20161	11.04	.2016	Statistics
T-220-VLN2	Semester Pro	ject 2			8	Completed	150-183/230	6	20161	31.05	.2016	Statistics
T-419-STR2	Discrete Math	ematics II			9	Completed	27-50/153	6	20161	14.04	.2016	Statistics
T-202-GAG1	<u>Databases</u>				8,5	Completed	40-67/223	6	20163	21.11	.2016	Statistics
T-301-REIR	Algorithms				9	Completed	22-40/208	6	20163	15.11	.2016	Statistics
T-303-HUGB	Software Eng	neering			8	Completed	52-92/219	6	20163	09.11	.2016	Statistics
T-308-PRLA	The Python P	<u>rogrammin</u>	g Language		8,5	Completed	34-43/99	6	20163	31.12	.2016	Statistics
T-317-CAST	Calculus and	Statistics			9	Completed	9-17/134	6	20163	24.11	.2016	Statistics
T-215-STY1	Operating Sys	tems				Transferred	N/A	6	20171	21.06	.2017	
T-513-CRNU	Cryptography	and Comp	uter Security			Transferred	N/A	6	20171	21.06	.2017	
T-622-ARTI	Artificial Intelli	g <u>ence</u>				Transferred	N/A	6	20171	21.06	.2017	
T-302-HONN	Software Desi	gn and Im	plementation		9,5	Completed	3-5/56	6	20173	14.11	.2017	Statistics
T-409-TSAM	Computer Net	works			8	Completed	34-50/172	6	20173	23.11	.2017	Statistics
T-488-MAPP	Mobile App D	<u>evelopmen</u>	<u>t</u>		9	Completed	5-8/40	6	20173	31.12	.2017	Statistics
T-514-VEFT	Web Services				9	Completed	12-25/93	6	20173	16.11	.2017	Statistics
T-636-SMAT	Human Comp	uter Intera	ction		9	Completed	1-2/19	6	20173	13.11	.2017	Statistics
T-404-LOKA	Final Project					Registered	N/A	12	20181			
T-427-WEPO	Web-Program	ming II			9,5	Completed	8-11/74	6	20181	20.04	.2018	Statistics
T-501-FMAL	Programming	<u>Language</u>	<u>s</u>		8	Completed	25-37/155	6	20181	13.04	.2018	Statistics
T-631-SOE2	Software Eng	neering II	- Testing		9	Completed	10-18/48	6	20181	09.04	.2018	Statistics
-406-IERP	Introduction to	ERP Sys	tems			Registered	N/A	6	20183			
T-316-UPPL	The Information	on and Tec	hnology Socie	ety.		Registered	N/A	6	20183			
T-542-HGOP	Introduction to	quality m	anagement ar	nd testin	9	Registered	N/A	6	20183			
		PREV.	THIS SEM.	NEXT	TOTALS	CATAGO	ORY	PF	REV. THIS S	EM. N	XT	TOTAL
Number of active ECTS		0	12	18	30	1. First cycle, introductory		ory	30	0	0	30
Total ECTS finished		138	18	0	156	2. First cycle, intermediate		ate	24	18	6	48
Total courses finished		23	3	0	26	3. First cycle, advanced			6	0	0	6

	PREV.	THIS SEM.	NEXT	TOTALS
Number of active ECTS	0	12	18	30
Total ECTS finished	138	18	0	156
Total courses finished	23	3	0	26
Average from finished courses	8,73	8,83	0,00	8,74

CATAGORY	PREV.	THIS SEM.	NEXT	TOTAL	
1. First cycle, introductory	30	0	0	30	
2. First cycle, intermediate	24	18	6	48	
3. First cycle, advanced	6	0	0	6	
TOTAL ECTS	60	18	6	84	